<resources>
    <string name="app_name">How It Ends</string>

    <string name="T1_Story">I was still learning about the great city. I had only been there for a year.So Building nilikuwa naishi kulikuwa na this Ghel, Stacey.Alikuwa ananikunywa ka nansez.Shida ni ati bado sikuwa nimeshapen jembe bana.Hunting skills zangu zilikuwa wanting, ata sikuwa naeza msalimia.She had 2 friends wenye walikuwa wanaishi kwa chuo. So weekend walikuwa wanakam kuspend time kwake.One day, one of her friends  knocked on my door and invited me to take Lunch with them.It was so uncomfortable for me, roho kudunda. Nikakula teke nikajitoa.</string>
    <string name="T1_Ans1">One of the girls alikuwa anaitwa Laveen and i never knew that she had a crush on me!</string>
    <string name="T1_Ans2">I liked Stacey so much but nilishindwa venye things could work out,coz she was too damn HOT</string>

    <string name="T2_Story">So when Stacy showed me, I was kinda confused.On a normal day,that would be a good thing. Laveen alikuwa from the lake side, sura ni a solid 5, lakini nyuma ni double cabin.Problem was I wanted Stacey juu alikuwa Mali Legit, so i couldnt make any move on Laveen , ndo nisichome bet ya Stacey..We started interacting with them more, one day wakanishow twende bike riding.Kumbe Laveen alikuwa na plan, the entire time alikuwa amenikwamilia kama kupe, ananishow turide kama tumeshikana mkono etc. Later that night nilikuwa nimechoka nikaoga nikaingia movie.</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans1">At about 11pm Laveen akakam kurequest anijoin</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans2">My mind was in chaos</string>

    <string name="T3_Story">Though nilikuwa nimejua ako na nigga.So day moja nigga wake akapata tukiwa na yeye, akajam sana kidogo apite na mimi.Skinny niggas tunaogopa vita kama ujimoto.Mi nikajitoa lakini hio stori haikunibamba.Juu huyo dem sikuwai mguza ,nikaamua  huyo nigga ata yeye atajua hajui, huezi nizidi nguvu na unizidi akili.Nikaanza kutext dem daily kumjulia hali and other stories.She got comfortable and even started sharing their issues with me,bad idea, hio nikama kunipea mwakenya,their relationship had been rocky for a couple of months and wasnt getting any better.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans1">Hii ikanifanya nibuild hopes</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans2">siku fulani dem akanicall kuniuliza kama nilikuwa free</string>


    <string name="T4_Story">I could not say no,but I promised myself i wouldnt touch her.Akanijoin kwa bed, movie ikaendelea.I started switching off, dem kujaribu kuguza Bosco na Haga, akapata niko social distancing...Sikua nadai anichomee bet bana. Next morning nikamshow I had my eyes on someone, she was heartbroken but it had to be done. Kuambia mabeshte wake ,Stacey akakam kuniuliza mbona nimeumiza her BFF, nikajikaza nikamshow yeye ndo nilikuwa nadai.Stacey akanishow hangenidate juu angeviolate Girl code.Girl code my ass! Niliboeka sana juu sasa bet yangu ilikuwa imeburn.Hio ubeshte kidogo nilikuwa na hio clique ikaisha,nikarudi default setting,LONE WOLF </string>
    <string name="T4_Ans1">One month later, dryspell imenitwanga pale BedSitter</string>
    <string name="T4_Ans2">Besides I was still a naive shy Boy</string>


    <string name="T5_Story">Dem akikuita na si sistako, beba tools, you never know.Nikatoka na blunts na tools nikaseti place hangeona.Kufika dem akanishow she was getting fed up with that Nigga.Good news Tukawasha nikaendelea kuskiza stress zake, telling her all the things she wanted to hear.Dem zake zikaanza kushika, akachomoa captain Morgan ikiwa nusu,kumbe alikuwa anakata before,kuongezea koro zikanasa kama nanzez.Nikamlalia kwa thighs akaendelea kunipasha stress zake.At first she was uneasy. after all we were just friends,Part of her wanted me to stop,but the other part was loving it.She couldnt resist though,i finally made it under her dress. </string>
    <string name="T5_Ans1">She was hot as fuck, completely irresistable</string>
    <string name="T5_Ans2">She was wearing a thong, i dont know why</string>

    <string name="T6_Story">I didnt have a meal,nikakumbuka Laveen,nikasaka number yake nikamtext. I asked her if the offer was still on the table, she said i only had to say the word. nikamshow if she was available that night tuchill.After an hour she was there kama alarm response crew. She made sure my eyes would be occupied on her greatest asset.Wueh ile dress alikuwa amedunga,madem wa lakeside wanakuanga blessed,tako kubwa na ni soft.She coooked but it was whack though, i didnt care, that was not the meal I was hungry for.Tukakula nikaingia shower.Kutoka nikapata dem ameeka tako on display kama denim za Gikomba.Wueh, askofu akasimama akainua towel,dem kuona akasmile. </string>
    <string name="T6_Ans1">Akaamua kuniangushia towel, nikajua its about to go down</string>
    <string name="T6_Ans2">Situations like this mtu unashindwa kuthink</string>

    <string name="T7_Story">Hio dress nikamtoa ,I went for her boob,one on my palm and the other one in my mouth. I didnt wanna make eye contact, It was controlled chaos.,her pussy was dripping wet, her heart beating first, she helped me remove my shirt and trouser,there was no stoping that train.Dem kuona Bosco anathrob,akachukua tools akanivalisha.Baas!Hio ni kama kupea messi freekick.I bent her over the study desk,nikasongesha thong kando,nikazama.Dem alikuwa wale wa kelele, kutangazia ploti.After establishing a rythm on backshots, nikashika braids,haga ilikuwa ile majimaji,Pah!Pah!Pah!, ungethani tunapiga makofi.Sijui huyo niga wake alikuwa na toothpick ama mimi ndo niko above average,ikus ilikuwa tight. </string>
    <string name="T7_Ans1">What drive men crazy</string>
    <string name="T7_Ans2">Ikus inakaza mjuols karibu ichome CD</string>

    <string name="T8_Story">She knew she wasnt my No 1 choice.She was yearning to impress kama Arsenal kujipata champions league final.Her mouth was doing magical things,ata sikuwa nakumbuka sura.She then kicked off the match with my favorite backshots.Its then that i realized she was ready to risk it all.Sex fantasies zangu nikaamua kurevisit,nilimgeuza venye nataka na hakuleta issue.Her skills were amazing. I discovered new angles especially for big asses,si mnajua vile zi husumbua,new positions,kujenga catalogue buana.Huyo dem Lungula alikuwa Fiti.</string>
    <string name="T8_Ans1">She did something unforgettable</string>
    <string name="T8_Ans2">Sijui alikuwa amefanya research ama</string>

    <string name="T9_Story">Dem alikuwa shape ya vera,ngozi nayo ilikuwa   nyororo ,msichana lightskinned, completely blessed in every angle.The girl of my dream was finally at my disposal.Yaani alikuwa na assets sexy ile design alikuwa akipenduka inajiggle ndani ya her tight mini.Akanikumbusha one of my favorite besties wa home, she was so reliable, we could do things that I couldnt do with my gf at that time.Mali safi na haisumbui.Unlike my Gf huyu dem alikuwa anipea bila complains.Manzi yangu hakuwa anapenda backshots, alikuwa analia ati Bosco anaumiza,Grace on the other side alikuwa aniekea arch ingine devilish,Wueh! </string>
    <string name="T9_Ans1">Besties can really be handy though</string>
    <string name="T9_Ans2">This lightskinned queens with soft skin...</string>

    <string name="T10_End">Mbegu zikiwa karibu kutoka alafu ulambwe masikio vizuri, wueh zinatokanga mpaka za the next round.It was at this moment that I realized I had rated her using the wrong parameter.Sura sio kila kitu.I should have given her a chance from the start, besides sura nzuri ni ya kuangalia tu.Your quality is determined by your performance on the big stage.Kuna madem sura nzuri lakini performance yao nikama Norwtch.Laveen had the assets and a sublime performance. </string>
    <string name="T11_End">Lazima ningepiga Round 2 kuconfirm.Dem akajilaza kifo cha mende. Deep strokes with transitions of speed and angling. She was loving it.Mjuols ilikuwa inajaribu kuchomoka inapatana na mikono kama mia, inarudishwa ndani..After round 2,nikajitoa,Round 3 haingeweza buana, na ningepatwa? Haakuna kitu kama ubeshte na dem, bora sio sitako,possibility ya mechi lazima iwe,beba tools just in case. Dem akiwa na maumivu ya roho, kama boychild, ni makosa sana kukosa kumpa DICKlofenac,it is the only way you can help. </string>
    <string name="T12_End">Gents kama umependa Dem na anakukunywa ile serious,dont lose hope if things dont seem to work out at the beginning.Kuwa mpole uone venye opportunity itajileta without even realizing it.</string>
    <string name="T13_End">My bestie, "Grace" could make my day much better than my Gf.She could stay from Thursday to sunday.Daily nilikuwa naamkia ikus without any limitations, surprise BJs, massage, huyu dem alikuwa dream girl.This always makes me wonder why Besties always play best and sweet roles in a relationship,They are always available to ensure you get whatever you need.</string>
    <string name="T14_End">Are always my weakness.Huwa wananikunywa hadi nafeel weakness kwa magoti, i never know why.Kwanza Stacey had this kind of smile that could make you her slave.Yaani ilikuwa ukieza pata opportunity with this Ghel, utaishi kuchapia macomrades vile uliangukia jackpot kibahati yenye ulistruggle excess but in the end it was worth it.Kujihisi tu Ku achieve your longterm DREAM  </string>
    <string name="T15_End">You ever asked yourself Mbona Bazenga Daudi wa Holy Book hangeresist bibi ya wenyewe akioga?Inakuanga the battle of two heads.My upper dude was like ,dude,you know its not right,but the other guy downstairs was like "Shut the fuck up , put her to sleep nigga.We all know the upper head never wins this argument,The guy downstairs can be very convincing. In adition a sexy bitch akiamua kukuseduce anakumaliza kisiasa.Hio ni kama pesa corruption, unajua ni mbaya lakini hauezi kataa.</string>
    <string name="T16_End">I was trying to think, but i couldnt. I told myself,"Maybe it is a set up", but I concluded, there was no way anybody could think of setting up a cabron like me.Nikifa nife,I let her do her thing.She was so passionate exactly what we like to see.</string>
    <string name="T17_End">Something that I regret and never forgive myself for such thing.Kukuwa mwanaume shy ni kitu mbaya sana, opportunity Zinaweza slip through fingers ubaki ukishangaa,like what the fuck Did I just Do!</string>
    <string name="T18_End">Also my love for FIFA ilinifanya that day after kutoka out na the ghels,nipitie kwa Beshte yangu fulani nikacheza kiasi before nifike kwa bedsitter yangu.That day was akward though juu beshte yangu fulani Voke Alinicheza hio FIFA ka nanzez,Nilitoka huko maboys wakinicheka juu ya ile design Voke alinichapa 10 nil,maboyz nayo  kuchachisha unaeza lia hadi.Ilibidi nimekaa tu kwa bedsitter yangu nikigonga maplans juu sikuwa na what next at the moment.</string>
    <string name="T19_End">Every man anakuanga na dream of one day, universe imwangushie the girl of his imagination. An exquisite hot girl mwenye mbogi itainamishia na kukusifu,mwenye figure kama ya pot,yaani shingo nyororo ya upanga with a round base, amebeba assets hadi akitembea unaenjoy the amazing appearance of the jiggling hot ass kwa dress,wueeh tanimaliza.Yaani kukaa na huyu dem ata one minute ilikuwa kinda impossible coz of the sexual tension yenye ilikuwa kwa environment.At that point what should be done MUST  be done</string>

</resources>